Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5685
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
  - Sub-Series B. Locals, 1971
    - Sub-Series 1. General Correspondence, 1971
      - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 59)
    - Sub-Series 4. Form letters, 1971
      - Form letters, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 60)
    - Sub-Series 7. Shop Correspondence, 1971
      - Borden, Inc., Lyons, New York, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 61)
        Proposed contracts for changes; notification of contract termination
      - Borden, Inc., Wellsboro, PA, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 62)
        Contract proposals; termination of contract notice; correspondence between Bernard Woolis and agents of the Allegheny Division re contract confusion about sick leave; Bernard Woolis & Richard Anderson re discharge of Grover Weller
      - Eastern Molded, Clearfield, PA, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 63)
        Workers engaged in an unlawful work stoppage led by Ralph Carbone
      - Eberle Tanning Co. Negotiations file #1, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 64)
        Contract agreement, December 1971, handwritten list of contract changes
      - Eberle Tanning Co. Negotiations file #2, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 65)
        Handwritten negotiations notes, December 3, 1970 - December 29, 1970; contract proposals October 1970
      - Eberle Tanning Co. Westfield, PA, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 66)
        More negotiation/contract proposal changes for the 1971 contract; notice of discharge of Earl D. Baker from K.W. Folger; correspondence re arbitration of discharged employees
      - Elkland Leather - Elkland, PA, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 67)
        Request for arbitrators to discuss the time standard dispute from Bernard Woolis; arbitration re handling of double butts on the bleach; resumes of potential arbitrators; Ralph Carbone, business agent, entered shop without consent and violated collective
      - E.H. Hall - Williamsport, PA, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 68-70)
        Contract proposals; Bernard J. Woolis affidavit between the NLRB; strike occurred the first week in May 1971 and compliance with sanction rules to obtain benefits; letter from Bernard J. Woolis to James O'Brien re union winning NLRB election and setting u
      - Franklin Tanning - Division of Hawes Leather Negotiation file; handwritten neg. notes, 8/13/71; contract proposals, 5/71; notice of work stoppage, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 71-72)
      - Howes-Franklin, Curwensville, PA, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 73-74)
        Arbitrator resumes; arbitrator parties correspondence over propriety of labor grades; contract agreement; request for strike sanction; list of reasons why labor relations are deteriorating
      - Howes-Pocahantus, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        To Bernard Woolis from Roger Tallman re contribution to pension plan
      - Howes-Stephenson & Osborne - Mt. Jewett, PA, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 2)
        Contract proposals; negotiation notes
      - Martin-Deichel - Middleville, New York, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        Contract proposals; discussion of proposed sewer project to alleviate fines and pollution for the Middleville plant
      - Parsons Tanning - Parsons, West Virginia, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 4-7)
        Contract proposals; certification results of election; requests for meetings by Bernard Woolis; Parson's negotiations, County Court House; stipulation of agreement
      - Superior Pet - Cunvensville, PA, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 8)
        Contract proposals; agreement on holiday payment
    - Sub-Series 8. Worker Correspondence, 1971
      Fur Dressers & Dyers Division - 48
      - Miscellaneous (general), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 9-15)
      - Form Letters, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 16-17)
    - Sub-Series Shop Correspondence - Notice of contract terminations, 1971
      - A-B, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Fur Processors Association, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 19-20)
      - Shapson - Collective Bargaining agreement, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Sub-Series Worker Correspondence, 1971
      Fur Dressers & Dyers Division - 88
      - Miscellaneous - piece work price lists, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 22-24)
      - Form Letters, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Sub-Series Shop Correspondence, 1971
      - A-D, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - DeGeorge, Stephen, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 27)
        Election materials, To Feinglass from Foner re election win in Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania
      - E-L, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - M-N, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - O-R, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - S-Z, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Sub-Series Worker Correspondence, 1971
      - A-Z, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - United Mechanics 150, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 33)
        Anthony Baratta - Personal to NYS Dept. of Taxation & Finance re non working days in NYS
      - Miscellaneous - correspondence, agreements, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - Woolis, Bernard - Personal, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 35-37)
        Paper - The Developing Crisis in International Trade Excerpt from "Stranger in the Promised Land" re Holiday in the USSR written by Franklin Garcia; thank you letters, requests for information, etc.
      - Form Letters, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Sub-Series Shop Correspondence, 1971
      - A, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 39)
      - Able Steel Equipment, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 40)
      - B, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 41)
      - Bestform Foundations of PA - Election material, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 42)
      - C-D-E, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 43)
      - F, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 44)
      - G-H, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 45)
      - I-J-K, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 46)
      - L-M, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 47)
      - Morse Negotiations, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 48-55)
        Correspondence from the contract negotiations from 1971 for Morse Electric, Ozone Park, New York. Includes drafts of proposed contracts, handwritten negotiations separated by day, proposals for each department, negotiation correspondence both within union
      - N, O, P, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 56)
      - R, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 57-60)
      - S, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 61)
      - Singer - NLRB, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 62)
        Demands (company), union includes employee benefit plan booklet; NLRB petition
      - Singer - Mount Vernon, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 63)
        Check off authorization cards; insurance enrollment card; addresses
      - Singer (Plainview), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 64)
        Check off dues; insurance; addresses
      - T-U, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 65)
      - V-Z, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 66)
      - Worker Correspondence, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 67)
- Series IV: District 2: Papers and Correspondence, 1940-1975
  - Allied Kid Company (AKC) Agreements, 1965-1975 (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - AKC Arbitration, 1940-1973 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - AKC Check-Off Lists, 1969-1975 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - AKC Election Campaign, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 5-8)
    Authorization cards; receipts for campaign expenses; names/addresses; propaganda from company/union; petition for certification; statement of employees regarding company conduct during the election campaign; letters from company to workers re union; lette
  - AKC Miscellaneous, 1963-1972 (Box 45, Folder 9-10)
    Frank Brownstone to Gorman re-election progress; Ernst & Ernst audit of Allied, 1963-65 from Bruce Stargatt (attorney) to Frank Kalsea re final contract agreement; contract proposals; financial statements; retroactive pay adjustments
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters (AMC), 1960-1968 (Box 45, Folder 11-16)
  - AMC - Contract Negotiations, 1958-1965 (Box 45, Folder 17-18)
    Negotiation notes; stipulations and amendments of contracts; contract; proposals
  - AMC - Election of 1966 Report, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - AMC - Financial, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    statement
  - AMC - Layoffs, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    Memo of agreement between union and management re cooperation of the two parties regarding layoffs and saving the company and seniority list
  - AMC - Pension, 1963-1969 (Box 45, Folder 22-27)
    Agreement between employer trustees and union trustees; correspondence re details of the agreement between union officials, employer, and the Bank of Delaware; correspondence re investment of funds and discussion of pooled funds; declaration of trust-vari
  - AMC - Vacation Pay, 1963-1968 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    Grievance re holiday pay; accrued vacation pay distribution to 52 employees; an attempt to claim these funds by the union as the Amalgamated Company faces bankruptcy
  - Arbitration and Contract Bills, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    Bills and arbitrators expenses
  - Bank Deposit Slip, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Blanchard Bros, 1957-1958 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    Job ratings and descriptions; arbitrators decisions-time study production and job evaluation
  - Blue Cross (NJ) Information, 1953-1963 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    Information given to members, notice of change in rates; plan administration correspondence
  - Brownstone, Frank - Communication, 1960-1967 (Box 45, Folder 33-36)
    International rep. in Philadelphia, District #2; correspondence from Chicago headquarters re various Amalgamated updates, questions about shop contract changes; financial reports for help in organizing plants; American Lace and Leather Co. Strike in VA an
  - Building Information, 1953-1969 (Box 45, Folder 37-38)
    Inspection reports, requests for licenses, purchase of buildings correspondence, etc.
  - Business Representatives Files, 1959-1967 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    Company and union meetings; enrollment cards - Camden Leather Workers Union; summaries of diner meetings - present were: Kartz, Gohron, Moorhouse, Kulesa & Elden
  - Camden Central Labor Union - Drug Programs, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 40)
    Proposal for a low cost medication program; updates on membership acceptance of program
  - Camden Central Labor Union - Financial, 1964-1967 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    Statements
  - Camden Central Labor Union - General, 1960-1974 (Box 45, Folder 42-43)
    Constitution; minutes, Swift boycott information; notice of meetings; 1968 Senate & Assembly bill opposed by the NJ State AFL-CIO; leather industry report
  - Canadian Amalgamated Conference, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Committee/Finance Reports for AMC, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Communications - CLWU Grievance slips/layoffs, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Communications - General, 1950-1975 (Box 46, Folder 3-5)
    Union members from Camden Leather Workers Union re various topics, abundance from the treasurer and business representatives
  - Conner, Hugh, 1968-1972 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Insurance information, including group insurance plan
  - Constitution - AMC Council 2 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Contributions - Charitable, 1957-1965 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    L201 requests to and thank you letters
  - Convention Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Preparation correspondence between Leon Schacter, International VP of AMC and Butcher Workers of N. America and Stephen Coule, another International Vice President; minutes of the pre-convention committee meeting, August 19, 1959
  - Correspondence from Senators, Congressman, etc., 1967-1969 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Letter from Frank Kulesa to Senator John Williams (Delaware) re leather, leather shoes imports; invitations and RSVP's to senators for Executive Board meetings
  - Coyle, Stephen J. - International AMC Vice President, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 11-13)
    Lists of membership by individual locals, state and international districts
  - Death Benefits, 1960-1968 (Box 46, Folder 14-15)
    Local 201 - correspondence from members re claims and union responses to inquiries
  - Delaware State Labor Council AFL-CIO, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    By-laws of council and income/expense sheet
  - Delaware Valley Tanning Corp. (DVTC) - Agreements, 1955-1968 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Local L206
  - DVTC - Elections, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Requests for nominations, signed petitions
  - DVTC - Employee List, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - DVTC Grievances, 1957-1968 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Grievance slips; NLRB charge against employer re termination of employees due to the transfer of work from Camden to new owner's of Philadelphia tannery; statement from Frank Kulesa; warning notices; letters from Frank Kulesa to management re various arbi
  - DVTC - Local 195 and Local 206 Agreements, 1966-1968 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Agreements
  - DVTC - Miscellaneous, 1959-1968 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - DVTC - Negotiating Committee Meetings Minutes, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - DVTC - Negotiations, 1955-1968 (Box 46, Folder 24-25)
    Notes and correspondence re negotiations of contracts; leather industry report prepared for the National Conference of AMC&BW of North America
  - DVTC - Shop Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Lists of members in attendance; minutes
  - Diamond State Tanning Co. (DSTC) - Agreements, 1955-1966 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - DSTC - Arbitrations, 1955-1970 (Box 46, Folder 28-30)
    Charge against union re seniority; correspondence between Cammer & Shapiro and DSTC re various resolutions of potential arbitration situations; routine notifications of upcoming arbitrations; charge against union re seniority and call-in pay
  - DSTC - Contract Negotiations, 1960-1970 (Box 46, Folder 31-35)
    Contract proposals, minutes of shop meetings re negotiations, notices of meetings, etc.
  - DSTC - Contract Stipulations, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 36)
    Stipulations re new job rates/wage changes
  - DSTC - Financial, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - DSTC - Miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    Names and addresses, correspondence request for a loan through the small business administration and denial
  - DSTC - Pension Plan/Payroll Audit, 1967-1970 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - DSTC - Receipt and Release Statements, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 40-44)
    re liability of company or union regarding the pension plan
  - DSTC - Worker Correspondence, 1960-1970 (Box 46, Folder 45)
    Notifications of termination, leaves of absence
  - Dinner Correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 46, Folder 46-50)
    Invitations and RSVP's to the Executive Board Dinner
  - Disability forms (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - District #2 - Copies of Letters, 1958-1965 (Box 46, Folder 52-58)
    Union correspondence and reports; resolutions on organization, civil rights, full employment, shorter work week, and the American economy; miscellaneous union expense and financial records
  - District #2 - Dinner and Meeting Reservations, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 59)
  - Dues, AMC&BW of NA, 1969-1974 (Box 46, Folder 60)
    Shortages, receipts, authorization check-offs and partially paid initiation fees
  - Employment Security Commission/Dues, 1968-1970 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - Evans, Jan R., Attorney, 1972-1974 (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Letters to L700
  - Executive Board Bulletins - AMC, 1959-1975 (Box 46, Folder 63-64)
    Meetings, arbitrations, correspondence, progress report
  - Executive Board Member Correspondence - AMC, 1965-1967 (Box 46, Folder 65)
  - Expenses and Communications, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Reports, events and scholarship announcements, receipts
  - Feinglass, Abe - Statement before Ways and Means Committee, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 2-5)
  - Goggie and Race Associates, Inc. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Investigation and report for John R. Evans and Co.
  - Good McCree Leather, Co., 1956 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Enrollment cards, employee lists, NLRB - union correspondence
  - Gorman, Patrick E., 1965-1969 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    AMC/AFL-CIO correspondence, Chicago Civic News; 1965 roll call; the Economic Outlook
  - Grays, Clifford, 1966-1969 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    Grievance awarded by arbitration through CLWU, L-206
  - Insurance - Coyle, Stephen, 1956-1964 (Box 47, Folder 10-11)
    Legal correspondence and letters; Executive Board bulletins
  - International Audits, 1965-1970 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - International Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - International Letters, 1965-1975 (Box 47, Folder 14-16)
    Merger agreement between AMC&BW of NA, AFL-CIO and United Packinghouse, Food & Allied Workers, AFL-CIO; employment survey; international union correspondence
  - International Officers; Executive Board Members, 1965-1968 (Box 47, Folder 17-20)
    Correspondence, executive bulletins; a proposed amendment to the AMC Constitution
  - J.E. Rhoads and Sons, Inc. - Agreements with Local 201, 1963-1965 (Box 47, Folder 21-22)
  - J.E. Rhoads and Sons, Inc. - Local 201 Check-offs, 1969-1970 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - J.E. Rhoads and Sons, Inc. - Local 201 Conner, Hugh (mail), 1970 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - J.E. Rhoads and Sons, Inc. - Local 201 Contracts, 1956-1968 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - J.E. Rhoads and Sons, Inc. - Local 201 Miscellaneous, 1942-1968 (Box 47, Folder 26-29)
    Special shop meetings, minutes; notices and correspondence; attendance sheets and employee lists
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Arbitration Cases, 1948-1967 (Box 47, Folder 30-35)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Assorting Dept., 1960-1966 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Beam House, 1959-1961 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Brushing Dept., 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Bundling Averaging Dept., 1966 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Closing of, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Contracts and Manuals, 1956-1959 (Box 47, Folder 41-46)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Dispute Involving Alfred Fanelli, 1944-1954 (Box 47, Folder 47-48)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Flat Average Workers, 1964-1967 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - History (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Ironing Dept., 1959-1961 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Job Descriptions, 1958-1964 (Box 47, Folder 52-64)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Job Postings, 1963-1966 (Box 47, Folder 65)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Machines, 1964-1967 (Box 47, Folder 66)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Miscellaneous, 1968-1965 (Box 47, Folder 67-68)
    Earned hours; job classifications and descriptions; leave of absence policies, procedures, and forms
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Negotiations, 1958-1970 (Box 47, Folder 69-78)
    General negotiation correspondence and agreements; leather industry reports; benefit information
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Peerless Seasoning, 1959-1963 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Pressing, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Putting Up, 1963-1968 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Ruby Seasoning, 1958-1960 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Ruby Tanning, 1957-1960 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Seniority Lists, 1966-1968 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Shipping and Assorting, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Shipping Room, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Shop Committee Meetings, 1941-1966 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Stake and Toggle Help, 1959-1963 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Suede Tanning, 1958-1961 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Swatch Books, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Trade Talk Pamphlet, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - J.R. Evans and Co. - Warehouse, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Julius Brand Leather Co. - Contracts and Negotiations, 1959-1972 (Box 48, Folder 15-17)
  - Julius Brand Leather Co. - Miscellaneous, 1960-1975 (Box 48, Folder 18-21)
    Julius Brand Leather Co. - Union correspondence, election slips; arbitration; memos; grievance slips; request for strike sanction; job classification factors
  - Julius Brand Leather Co. - Warning Notices, 1965-1972 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Jurisdictional Dispute between Local 464 and Local 474, 1954-1962 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Kulesa, Frank (later President of Local 206) - Correspondence, 1940-1969 (Box 48, Folder 24-27)
    E.F. Houghton company rates; Charles Bond Co. agreements; medical plan; leather worker flyer; pictures of Local 206 flyer urging DVTC employees to end strike
  - Kulesa, Frank - Financial, 1947-1971 (Box 48, Folder 28-30)
  - Kulesa, Frank - Interdepartmental Meetings, 1965-1968 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Kulesa, Frank - International Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Kulesa, Frank - Miscellaneous, 1963-1967 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    Correspondence; Executive Board bulletin
  - Kulesa, Frank - Personal, 1955-1970 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Kulesa, Frank - Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 35-36)
    Letters to Abe Feinglass, Leon Schachter, and Stephen Coyle; minutes; memos
  - Kulesa, Frank - Staffgrams, 1967-1969 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - Lackawanna Leather Co., Hockettstown - Contract Proposals and Resolutions, 1955-1975 (Box 48, Folder 38-47)
  - Lackawanna Leather Co., Hockettstown - Miscellaneous, 1956-1969 (Box 48, Folder 48-51)
    Enrollment cards; correspondence; newspaper article about pay increase; administrative fee schedule; receipts; grievance slips; meeting minutes
  - Lackwanna Leather Co. - Reports, 1956-1970 (Box 48, Folder 52-54)
    Job descriptions and evaluations, piece work rates
  - Landrum Griffin Labor Bill, 1959-1965 (Box 48, Folder 55-57)
    Pamphlets; labor organization annual report; Public law 86-257; a bill to amend the Social Security Act and the Internal Revenue code to provide better insurance; AMC&BW of NA membership summary; executive incomes; wage structure
  - Leather Finishing Co. - Agreements, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 58-59)
  - Leather Finishing Co. - Correspondence, 1958-1968 (Box 48, Folder 60)
  - Legislative Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Letters to All Plants, 1967-1975 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Local 27 (Newark, NJ) and Local 52A Merger Correspondence, 1953-1970 (Box 49, Folder 3-4)
    Agreement
  - Local 34L (Hoboken, NJ) ,R. Neumann and Co. Correspondence, 1953-1970 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Local 72F (Washington, Dc) - Correspondence, 1957-1968 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Local 117 (Baltimore, MD), 1963-1967 (Box 49, Folder 7-10)
    Procedure for reporting labor disputes; meeting minutes; grievance reports; financial reports; correspondence
  - Local 201 - Arbitration, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Local 201 - Correspondence, 1957-1967 (Box 49, Folder 12-14)
    Letter, notices, annual report; pension plan
  - Local 201 - Election Committee, 1960-1970 (Box 49, Folder 15-16)
  - Local 201 - Financial Statement, 1969-1971 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Local 201 - Meeting Notices, 1953-1966 (Box 49, Folder 18-22)
  - Local 201 - Members Attending Meetings List, 1954-1970 (Box 49, Folder 23-24)
  - Local 201 - Members Attending Special/Shop Meetings List, 1966-1970 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Local 201 - Merger Papers, 1970-1971 (Box 49, Folder 26-27)
  - Local 201 - Miscellaneous, 1960-1964 (Box 49, Folder 28-29)
    Convention call; correspondence; resolutions; Wilmington Enameling Co. agreement
  - Local 201 - Real Estate, 1968-1969 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Local 201 - Resolution of Merger Agreement of Locals 34, 101, 206, 208, 475, 201, and 72 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Local 201 - Resolution of Merger - Constitution (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Local 201 - Seniority List and Employee Duties for Amalgamated Leather Companies Inc., 1966 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Local 201 - Unemployment Insurance, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Local 201 - Vouchers, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Local 206 (Camden, NJ) - Board Correspondence/Fines and Dues, 1942-1947 (Box 49, Folder 36-39)
  - Local 206 - Executive Board Meetings, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    Financial report
  - Local 206 - Miscellaneous, 1950-1963 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    Posters and flyers; pictures
  - Local 206 - Quakertown Division Communications, 1968-1975 (Box 49, Folder 42-44)
    Correspondence; notices; compensation agreements; group insurance plan; merger resolution
  - Local 206 - Quakertown Division Seniority List, 1970-1975 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Local 208 (Quakertown, PA) - Contracts with McAdoo and Allen Welting Co., 1955-1967 (Box 49, Folder 46)